Divya Prabha T

<u>divyaprabha.it2014@gmail.com</u> Mobile: +91-9600117891 Portfolio:http://portfolio.com

Professional Summary:

To engage myself in a challenging work environment where I can build a portfolio of projects demonstrating proficiency in both front end using HTML, CSS, and Java script. I have 5 years of professional work experience as Web Designer. I have domain experience in creating websites for Hotels, Automobiles and Organization.

Technical Skills:	
Front End	HTML,CSS,JavaScript,ReactJs
Back End	NodeJs
Database	MySQL,MongoDB
Framework	Bootstrap, Joomla, Word Press
Others	Git, Visual Studio, Render, Netlify

Employment Summary:

Web Designer in High Think Media Box, Coimbatore, India from April 2019 to September 2019.

Web Designer in Vconnect Media, Coimbatore, India from October 2017 to January 2019.

Web Designer in W3cert Technologies, Erode, India from February 2016 to September 2017.

Web Designer in Scotwebtech, Erode, India from December 2014 to December 2015.

Project Description:

Project Title	Highthink
Project Link	https://highthink.in/
Client	High Think Media Box
Languages	HTML,CSS,JavaScript,Bootstrap
Role	Web Designer
Description	Creating a Organization website for High Think Media Box, a creative branding agency. The website offers to users to know about services provided by High Think Media Box. Users satisfaction is a primary goal to achieve, thus creating a smooth flow of website.

Responsibilities	 Get all the images from Graphic Designing Team
	Develop the websites using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.
	❖ Get the content for the all pages from the content writing team.
	Completed the websites, moved to server and support the Site.
Team Size	1

Project Title	E2E Events	
Project Link	https://e2eexcite.com/	
Client	E2E	
Framework	WordPress	
Role	Web Designer	
Description	Creating a website for Event organization to show their information like services, portfolio and contact information. Website is created using Wordpress. This design enhanced user experience by 80%.	
Responsibilities	 Get the images and content from the client side. Designed the layout using wordpress. After implemented and tested website upload to server. Changes done by the client wish. 	
Team Size		

Project Title	Scheppers Hotel
Project Link	https://www.scheppershotelrome.com/
Client	Fisheyes Scotland
Languages	HTML,CSS,Bootstrap,JavaScript,Jquery
Role	Web Designer

Description	Creating a website for Scheppers Hotel in Rome. This website offers to view Rooms details and Service details. Photo gallery tab created by using the Nivo light box. Since Book now page is already designed by Client, we tested the website and fixed the bugs for the same.	
Responsibilities	 Design the layout using code. Get the images, content and book now information. Tested the website from client format and fixed the bugs. After testing file, upload to server using Filezilla. 	
Team Size	4	

Certifications

Learning Full Stack Developer Course from Guvi, strongly enhancing my software development.

Education Summary:

Degree	Specialization	University	Year of passing	Percentage
UG	B.TECH IT	Anna	2014	7.65 CGPA
		University		
HSC	Science & Maths	State Board	2010	75
SSC	-	State Board	2008	83

Personal Information

Name:	Divya Prabha T
Sex:	Female
Marital Status:	Married
Address:	Door No: 6, Abinav Karthi Illam, Solar Pirivu, Karur Road, Near Vinayaga Driving School, Erode-638002.
Nationality:	Indian
Languages:	English, Tamil